## Joshua Duncan

WEB AND GRAPHIC DESIGN - GALLERY SALES

**BUSINESS MANAGEMENT** 

(435) 503-1978

jduncan97@gmail.com

inkedin.com/in/jduncan-9720

github.com/jduncan9720

Heber City, UT 84032

#### **EDUCATION**

FULL STACK WEB
DEVELOPMENT
CERTIFICATE
UNIVERSITY OF UTAH

2020

BUSINESS MANAGEMENT
ASSOCIATES DEGREE
UTAH VALLEY UNIVERSITY

1997

## TECHNICAL SKILLS

HTML, CSS
Javascript

MongoDB, MySQL

Express

NODE

React.js

Bootstrap.js

Adobe Photoshop

Adobe Indesign

Adobe Illustrator

Microsoft Office

Ouickbooks

Social Networking

#### **INTERESTS**

Time with Family Hiking & Fishing Skiing Gaming

Music & Concerts

Travel

#### PROFILE SUMMARY

Dedicated, proactive business management and web development professional whose 20-year record includes, establishing and maintaining workings of both new and existing businesses, designing products and marketing materials for print and web applications, creating user friendly websites, and successful sales of high value artwork. Effective communicator with the ability to work with customers and co-workers at all levels. A results-focused, creative individual with excellent leadership and organizational skills. Recently completed a Full Stack Web Development course through the University of Utah.

#### EXPERIENCE

#### **BUSINESS MANAGER - WEB AND GRAPHIC DESIGNER**

ROBERT DUNCAN STUDIOS // MIDWAY, UT // 1998 - PRESENT ( CURRENTLY PART-TIME )

- Work with owner and employees to create and achieve company goals
- Organize and keep inventory of over 200 prints, cards, and yearly calendars
- Design and maintain an ecommerce website offering over 200 products
- Design promotional email blasts and maintain customer database
- Create and oversee printing of all retail products and advertising material
   Control all organization and storage of all media files and backups
- Design and oversee printing of 15,000 yearly retail wall calendars.
- Manage all printing, color checks and quality control with local printing companies
- Past travel to Hong Kong to oversee printing of yearly calendars
- Clear product through international shipping and customs
- Cultivate and manage relationships with retail and wholesale clients
- Manage all day to day operations of professional publishing business.

#### **DIRECTOR OF SALES**

MOUNTAIN TRAILS GALLERY // PARK CITY, UT // 2014 - PRESENT

- Sell and promote original artwork and sculptures from over 60 different artists
- Demonstrate to clients the value of \$3000 \$150,000 artwork
- Maintain website and online inventory management
- Design print advertisements for national art magazines
- Assist clients with home consultations and installations of artwork
- Work with high end clientele in sales and customer service from beginning to end
- Maintain clients trust while working inside private communities and homes in the Park City area while overseeing installations and deliveries of artwork.

# Joshua Duncan

WEB AND GRAPHIC DESIGN - GALLERY SALES
BUSINESS MANAGEMENT

(435) 503-1978

jduncan97@gmail.com

in linkedin.com/in/jduncan-9720

github.com/jduncan9720

Heber City, UT 84032

### COMMUNITY SERVICE

#### **BOARD MEMBER**

CHARLESTON WATER
CONSERVANCY DISTRICT
Heber City, UT
2013 - Present

### EXPERIENCE (continued ....)

#### ART CONSULTANT

MANGELSEN IMAGES OF NATURE // PARK CITY, UT // 2011 - 2014

- Sell and promote the high end limited edition photography of Tom Mangelsen
- Home consultations and installation of artwork
- Work consistently with high end clientele in sales and customer service
- Top selling part-time employee for 2013

#### **DELIVERY DRIVER**

PRINTING RESOURCE // LINDON, UT // 1997 - 1998

- Organize and deliver printed material
- Meet customer deadlines